hi and welcome to living in Central
Texas I'm Andrea dudic a realtor and
Associate broker with Vista Real Estate
and today I'll be showing you one of my
newest and cutest listings in belon
Texas now if you're new to my channel
don't forget to like this video
subscribe and click the Bell icon so you
can stay up to date on all things
happening in Central Texas so if you're
looking for peaceful country living but
you want to be close to Modern amenities
this may be the perfect home for you
you're just outside of City Limits so
you have super low taxes you're super
close to all amenities um you're about 5
minutes away from still house Hollow
Lake if you like camping fishing hiking
you're about 25 minutes from Fort
Cavazos formerly Fort Hood an hour
outside of Austin Texas and about 45
minutes to an hour away from Waco now
some of my favorite parts of this
property are that it's on 8/10 of an
acre so it's a very large lot lots of
things that you could do to the property
this home is really cool cuz it also has
a storm shelter while we do get
tornadoes here storm shelters are
actually pretty hard to find this home
is so cute I can't wait to show you and
I really hope you love it let's take a
look this adorable Farmhouse at 3200
Auction Barn Road in belon Texas was
built in 1999 there's four bed 2 and 1/2
bath plus a formal dining space
[Music]
when the sellers purchased this home
they actually removed one of the walls
making the space extra inviting and more
open than it previously was which I
think definitely helped with the space
[Music]
the master suite is located on the first
floor which is a nice little peaceful
Retreat from the rest of the home
[Music]
he
there are gorgeous wood floors
throughout the main living areas and the
downstairs master bedroom and there is
brand new carpet um in the secondary
bedrooms
[Music]
outside the backyard offers Endless
Possibilities with a newly laid 20x 40
concrete slab ready for your outdoor
kitchen where work shop or whatever you
can
[Music]
imagine there's also an underground
storm seller for added piece of find for
the occasional Texas
tornadoes and of course you'll love the
front porch just waiting for your
morning coffee
[Music]
thank you so much for joining me on this
property tour today I'd really love your
feedback on this home and to hear what
you want to see more of do you want to
see more unique properties like this do
you want to see more new construction
let me know I'd love to show you you can
find all my contact information below
until next time I'm Andrea dudic
associate broker with f real estate
[Music]